♫ Oh. my God.
please help me ♫
♫ Knee deep in the river
trying to get clean ♫
♫ He says. wash your hands.
get out the stains ♫
♫ But you best believe. boy.
there's hell to pay ♫
♫ Yeah. you best believe. boy.
there's hell to pay. saying ♫
♫ Oh. my God.
please help me ♫
♫ Neck deep in the river
screaming for relief ♫
♫ He says. it's mine to give
but it's yours to choose ♫
♫ You're gonna sink or swim.
you're gonna learn the truth ♫
♫ No matter what do.
you're gonna learn
the truth. saying ♫
♫ Ate the bread
that once was stones ♫
♫ Fell from a cliff.
never broke a bone ♫
♫ Bowed down to get
the kings overthrown ♫
♫ And I'm all alone
and the fire grows ♫
All right. McBride.
You're out.
Okay. Excellent.
I'm running a little behind.
I'm gonna trust that you didn't
screw me on my shit here. okay?
The judge dismissed it.
Mr. McBride.
You missed it.
You gotta be shitting me.
What the fuck happened?
- What happened to my car?
- Came in that way.
Oh. bullshit.
It didn't come in
in that way.
My goddamn windshield
wasn't broken.
The fuckin' headlight
wasn't out.
Look at this shit.
There's fuckin' dents in it.
What's going on here. huh?
Look. Sign the form.
How's your bite feeling?
You go to the doctor yet?
I'm fine. Dad.
Really. it didn't
even hurt that bad.
Mom wasn't too excited
about the whole thing. though.
Look. I just don't want you
walking around
thinking it was my fault at all.
because you saw the guy...
- Dad. please don't.
- You saw the son of a bitch.
Don't.
How about your mom?
What is she saying?
Don't do that. either.
I don't know.
I'm just sorry the whole
thing happened. honey.
Okay.
So we're good?
Yeah. Dad.
We're good.
- Hey. Dad?
- Yeah.
Get your shit together.
No housekeeping today. okay?
- I said no housekeeping!
- What. you couldn't call me?
You couldn't let me know
what's going on?
If I had known
that you'd been arrested.
I could have done something!
I could have moved the hearing!
You get one call. man!
And you can't fucking use it?
Could you keep your fucking
voice down?
Fuck you. keep you voice down!
There's no law that says
they gotta give me a phone call.
I was resisting arrest.
They ain't got do me
no favors.
- How drunk were you?
- Not at all!
I haven't really had a drink
in three days.
- Where's Rachel?
- What do you care?
You fuck her.
And you don't show up
for her case.
You're fucked up
and you're sick.
And you made me look like
a fucking idiot!
I'm coming up
with a plan to fix it.
'cause I actually do care.
Oh. I understand.
I understand.
Because you're gonna fucking
fix it. 'cause I tell you what.
I didn't get to where I am
by letting assholes like you
drag me down.
Where you are?
You got a one-woman shop
in fuckin' Van Nuys. honey.
Fix it!
Or I swear to fucking God...
I swear to God...
I'm gonna make your life
shittier than it is now.
Believe it or fuckin' not.
You'd have to be
a goddamn magician to do that.
- Malicious prosecution.
- Malicious prosecution?
For starters.
And anything else
you can think of.
Okay. First of all.
I don't think that failure
to show up at a court date
constitute...
The case is dead. Donald.
It's dismissed.
Be a gracious one.
and let's just let
sleeping dogs lie.
Some dogs refuse to lie.
Some dogs you have to hit.
kick while they're down.
in order to ensure
they stay down.
I've known Billy longer
than any of you.
longer even than you.
I know what he's capable of.
For good and ill.
He's a moral leper.
Billy created this firm.
I created this firm.
That's why my name is first.
The point is. whatever
your feelings are for Billy...
My feelings are not in play.
Michelle.
Are yours?
I don't want any claim filed.
If you file a claim.
then I have to report it
back to Borns Tech
where I will be met with "why."
It is not a satisfactory
response on my part
to say I have no fucking idea.
If they ask you why...
you just tell them
because I said so.
- Listen. please.
- No.
- Hear me out.
- Mm-hmm.
I gotta a plan.
We're gonna go back
to state court.
I'm gonna get
the hearing rescheduled.
And then at the same time.
Rachel... Listen!
I'm gonna file in federal court
with an entirely different
theory.
Now. if none of that works.
you just sue me for malpractice.
I got professional insurance.
I'll go along with
whatever you say.
And then you get something
for your case.
- You think I did this
for money?
- No.
I'm making money
off my dead brother?
That's not what I'm saying!
Hang on a second! Please!
I never missed a court date
in my lifetime.
- Bullshit.
- That's not bullshit.
- I don't believe you.
- I always made it.
Maybe I was
in bad shape sometimes.
but I always answered
the fucking bell. Rachel.
And as far as... Look.
I also...
There's this guy...
There's this guy that's been
following me around. Okay?
I've seen him three times.
The first time was at the bar.
He's glaring at me
at everything.
At first. I thought he was
just some fucking asshole.
But then. sure enough.
he's outside.
he's taking pictures.
I'm with my kid.
He's creeping around
out there all night.
And last night.
he was in my cell.
There's gotta be something
to it.
It's gotta have something
to do with the case.
I know it does.
- We got something...
- You need more help than I do.
Rachel?
Hey! Idiota! Quit it.
Fucking seals won't
go away. man.
I fucking hate seals.
What's up. man?
Oh. no. No.
Get the fuck outta here.
We don't need anything from you.
I'm not here to see you.
I'm here to see him.
I told you. man.
He isn't against moving shit.
It's just that
he don't know you.
You know how many guys
out there would be willing
to make this deal?
It's not my boat. man.
It's my brother's boat.
Can't blame him. either.
How do we know you're
not some kind of cop?
Just show up here
with this deal out of nowhere?
Dude. we don't know you.
My brother's careful.
He's got his wife.
Got kids.
He's actually kind of
a pussy now.
If you don't handle deals
like this.
why do you have a guy like
Billy McBride working for you?
- Who?
- He's a lawyer.
He's the one who told me
you guys would be open
for this deal.
He's a drug lawyer.
He's big.
I don't know any lawyers. man.
Don't bullshit me.
I met the guy one time.
He came by here and wanted
to talk about an accident
we had on our old boat.
That's it.
Okay.
What'd you tell him?
Woman: That was the last
time I spoke to her.
Man: That was very brave.
Thank you. Candace.
Is there anyone else
that would like to speak?
I recognize some of you
from the old days
when I used to come
to this meeting.
I figured I'd either die
or come back when I hit
rock bottom.
which I did a few times.
But I just kept redefining
what rock bottom is.
Kind of like God's little acre.
Maybe that's a little obscure
for some of you younger folks.
And recently I had
a pretty good chance
to come back.
I got some decent work.
Got a girl that would
half-assed tolerate me.
But I fucked it up.
You know. aren't you all
tired of saying
the same shit over and
over at these meetings?
I know I'm tired of hearing it.
Truth is. I wanna get my shit
together for my daughter's sake.
And I wanna get back to being
somebody that people can trust.
So that's kind of my deal.
- Hey. Alma. you got a sec?
- No.
Listen. I wanna apologize
to you for missing
the court date.
Don't talk to me.
Mr. McBride.
- Listen. I need a favor.
- You're not getting one.
I gotta go back
in front of Keller.
He's not gonna like it.
but you gotta do this for me.
No.
I'm calling on you for a favor.
and you know exactly
what I'm talking about.
- You gonna do it or not?
- Or what?
Are you threatening me?
I don't wanna have to.
but I will.
- After you.
- Thanks.
Okay. so just a recap.
Great freeway. access.
- Right?
- Right.
And you saw the light inside.
Gorgeous.
And the public schools
are on the up.
Excuse me for one...
No. Nope. Nope. No.
This is a shown by... No.
What? Did you fix it?
If not. fuck off.
Not yet. But I filed a new case
in federal court
based on the death
on the High Seas Act.
- High sea what?
- I'll explain it to you.
Look. I just need you
to help me get Rachel back.
- I've been trying
and it ain't working.
- Right.
Well. I don't blame her. Hey!
Why don't you guys go inside.
have another look around.
and I'll be right in. okay?
Okay.
I'm trying to make amends here.
If you want me to apologize to
you too. I will. I'm sorry.
I don't accept.
I've been having
kind of a rough time.
I need a little help.
Oh. so you're the victim?
Is that right?
Look. I know all about guys
like you.
I've married two of them. and...
Forget it.
I'll figure out a way to get
the case reheard without you.
Patty...
We can do this.
I guarantee you.
I just need you
to help me get Rachel back.
Fine.
- I'll be right here.
- Whatever.
Cooperman asked for me again?
Why?
Seems he's a fan.
Malicious prosecution...
and whatever else
you can throw at them.
Billy's just tried to resurrect
the case in federal court
under the High Seas Act.
So. while you're at it. you can
draft a response to that.
as well as the motion
to dismiss.
and we'd like it all
by the end of business.
- Okay.
- Really?
'Cause you look a little bit
like a deer in the headlights.
It's just that...
I've never even seen the man.
Well. it seems
you're on his radar.
Which could either be
very good or very bad.
Donald hates Billy McBride
more than any human
on the earth.
And Donald is one of life's
truly magnificent haters.
Just imagine how happy
he would be if you help bury
his biggest enemy.
End of business.
Best way not to get a DUI is
to drink at home.
- I was set up. Frankie. okay?
- Why?
I don't know.
I'm still trying
to figure that out.
Hey. I need you to stop
calling me. okay?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about calling me
and hanging up like
a teenage boy.
I called you a couple of times.
I left a message.
but I didn't hang up on you.
Really? You didn't call me
and hang up? It wasn't you.
No. I swear to God.
Did you hope it was?
Tell the truth.
Hmm.
I'll stay for one second.
- Federal court.
- Yeah.
- You think we can win?
- I know we can.
Okay.
Hey. look. I'm sorry
about coming over there
and acting like some tweaker
or something.
It's okay.
If I didn't give a shit.
- I'd just give it up. you know?
- I know.
Your face okay?
Yeah. it's fine.
I'm lying. It sucks.
That feels like shit.
I mean. the sleep apnea
and everything
- and the busted nose...
- Not good.
- Bad combination.
This thing. um...
This thing we did together.
you and me...
- Sex?
- Yeah.
If we're gonna be back
in business here.
probably should shy away
from that.
Yeah. Totally.
Understood.
I agree.
It was kind of fun. though.
wasn't it?
♫ If you're feeling
kind of low ♫
♫ Kind of down ♫
- Hurt?
- No. it's okay.
- Thanks for doing this.
- Yeah.
God. I'm being followed.
and you're having people
hang up on you.
It just. um...
I've never been stalked.
Yeah.
Me neither.
You think it's the case?
I can't imagine it's not.
♫ I don't wanna see you blue ♫
You're a sweet guy.
- You are.
- Come on.
Patty said that juries
used to love you.
But what happened?
She's right. They did.
Juries loved me.
And I loved them. too.
That's the secret.
At one point.
they loved me so much.
I could do anything I wanted.
just about. yeah.
But that can be dangerous.
I won't say anything
if you don't.
I won't say a word.
♫ To see you smile ♫
Have you actually met him?
No. but maybe I will.
Has anybody ever seen Cooperman?
He won't let himself be seen.
Supposedly.
half his face is burnt off.
Some injury in Vietnam.
He sits in a dark room all day.
I heard he has hepatitis
and light sensitivity.
I heard the partners make him
stay in the room.
because he's out of his mind.
And it was Billy McBride
who drove him nuts.
I even heard it was McBride
who lit his face on fire.
and they made up
the whole Vietnam story.
That's definitely not true.
Yeah. Luce. you gotta take a
picture if you ever meet him.
Oh. yeah.
I'm gonna whip out my phone
and send you a Snapchat?
Don't worry.
That's never going to happen.
because he does not exist.
You know who doesn't exist.
Sumi? You.
In fact. none of you exist.
Unless we count flecks.
We don't count flecks.
Specks. we count.
Lucy. here.
has clawed her way up
from being a fleck
to a little speck.
Did you file the answer
in federal court?
- Yeah. last night.
- Good.
Flecks.
Oh. fuck.
Okay. You guys can't hang out
in here anymore.
- She's not coming back.
- Seriously. get out.
- I'm not a fleck.
- Rules.
How many times I gotta say this?
I don't argue.
Okay? I paper. I plead.
and I settle.
Seriously.
If I'm your strategy.
then you gotta get
a new strategy.
- Hey.
- Hey. what's up?
- Oh. hi.
- Billy. this is Marva.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
Good. How are you?
And this is Patty Salton
something.
- No.
- Okay. Hi.
Marva has agreed to take over.
Take over what?
She'll be my replacement.
She has considerable experience
as a legal secretary.
- And I...
- Come here a sec. Brittany.
I wanna ask you something.
Come here.
I gotta go back to my other job.
Right?
We agreed on a temporary basis.
- What's up?
- I gotta get on
with my life. Billy.
You said for one case.
which I did.
Yeah. and we're not done.
We gotta go
to federal court now.
I... Billy. I need
to make a living.
Well. you're gonna make
a living. I told you.
This is a real
fucking case here.
You're gonna get paid.
I promise.
- I have clients of my own.
- I know that.
But I thought
we had something here.
Besides. look at
this fucking woman.
Look how goddamn big she is.
- This is a little
fuckin' place.
- Hey. Shh!
No disrespect. but fuck.
You gotta stay with me here.
honey. Please.
It's really not fair
for you to beg like that.
'cause you know I owe you.
Come on.
Fine.
But Marva stays and I train her.
It's fine by me.
Hey. Jason. Hi.
My God. look at you.
you got so tall.
Give me a hug. Hi.
Good to see you.
God. you look so much
like your dad.
Rachel.
Hey. um...
Hi. Gina.
I hope it's okay.
No. it's not.
- Mom. please.
- Jason. go inside.
Now. I'll be in in a minute.
It's good to see you.
This is rude.
You're just stopping by
without calling first?
I did call. Gina.
you don't return my calls.
That didn't stop you
from coming. did it?
I just thought that you both
deserve to understand what's
going on.
We don't want to have anything
to do with you or your bullshit
case.
Ryan didn't kill himself.
He wouldn't kill himself.
He loved Jason too much.
- He loved you too much.
- I know that.
I actually have
his suicide note upstairs.
Do you wanna read it again?
Do you wanna read about how much
he hated what he was doing?
How much he hated himself?
Do your lawyers even know
about the note?
Oh. Jesus.
Do you have any idea
how much this hurts us?
How much this hurts Jason?
Just go.
The room key.
- He checked in yet?
- No.
- Thank you. sweetie.
- Of course.
♫ Baby. bodies aren't just
for sleeping ♫
♫ It's been a year
since I really rolled out
♫ Yeah ♫
♫ Ooh. but it took
a long turning 'round ♫
♫ It's only unattainable love ♫
Pretty.
Pretty woman.
Yeah.
I'll just be...
God damn. they rigged these
fuckin' blood test results.
- Billy.
- I wasn't drunk.
Okay. look.
I will handle the DUI.
Okay? That I can do.
What was your blood alcohol?
You just handle the federal
case. Let me worry about
the DUI.
Why are you being so dumb?
My entire practice is dealing
with DUIs.
Excuse me. hon.
I don't see anywhere
here in your pleading
where you say that there
was a wrongful act.
A man blew up on a boat
owned by the defendant.
Res ipsa.
Something wrong happened.
It's obvious.
That's all you got?
Something wrong happened?
- I'll just handle
the federal case. too.
- Fuck you. Billy.
"Fuck you" is good in traffic.
but not in court. okay?
In the real world. lawyers
have to argue cases and shit.
Thank you.
Thank you for your wisdom.
Honey. I was doing this shit
back when you were wondering
why Ken and Barbie
didn't have genitals.
I used to handle
20 cases at a time.
I think I can handle two.
- Jesus Christ.
- Billy?
Talk to you for a second?
- Okay. let's have it.
- Okay.
- Denise was pretty shaken up.
- Yeah. so was I.
She was tased. Billy.
Well. I wasn't drunk. okay?
She could have been
seriously hurt...
Yeah? Well. talk to your
goddamn boss about that.
You are insane. if you think
that Donald Cooperman has
some conspiracy against you.
insane!
Okay. Well. let me explain
something to you.
Ever since I took this case.
weird shit's happening
to me. okay?
People are following me.
I'm getting pulled over
by the cops.
having my ass beat.
- You're so crazy.
- Yeah?
- Let it go.
- It's not happening.
- No.
- You can't win this.
Yeah. maybe not.
But I'm sure as shit gonna try.
And let me tell you
something else.
As much as I'd like
to fuck Cooperman.
that's not the reason
I'm in this one.
I'm actually doing this again.
So get ready for it. will you?
I don't care why
you're in this one.
Just leave our daughter
out of it. okay?
Yeah. well. I kind of was.
And then you let her.
you know. get lost.
Sorry about the...
Don't worry about it.
It's okay.
I have some unsettling
and some good news.
Yeah? Well. give it to me.
The clerk from the federal court
just called to say
that the case
has been dismissed.
No explanation given.
Just dismissed.
I know. it's unsettling.
Well. what's the good news?
Your friend Alma called.
How the fuck did he get the case
reinstated in state court?
It was dead in state court.
I saw it die.
- And yet it lives.
- That's not an answer.
It wasn't actually dismissed
with prejudice.
It got kicked because
Billy didn't show up.
We refiled the motion
to dismiss.
We're back in there tomorrow.
This time it will be
squashed for good.
How do you know that?
Because the Gnome has
the assignment.
And Cooperman is the one
that got him the appointment.
Wait. The Gnome?
I don't like the Gnome.
He's a loose cannon.
We are gonna be fine. Leonard.
This should be settled.
Donald Cooperman
will not use our money
to fight his vendetta.
That not what this is about.
I don't care what this is about.
Donald Cooperman
can't let it go.
He is obsessing
over Billy McBride.
And I am telling you.
this thing could be
fucking us up the ass.
- Oof!
- Hard!
Leonard. sweetie.
Maybe this whole general
counsel gig isn't for you.
You don't seem to be having fun.
Do not handle me. Callie.
People should be happy
in life. that's all
I'm saying.
- The Gnome.
- Yeah. regardless.
And you say
he's Cooperman's friend?
Not necessarily.
Most of Cooperman's friends
hate his guts.
Keller's a decent judge.
He's just a nasty little prick.
Okay. so should we survive
the motion to dismiss
tomorrow. we settle.
- Right?
- Could be.
Let's assume for the sake
of argument
that you are everything
you're cracked up to be.
Let's even say you show up
to court tomorrow.
We are talking about one of the
top three law firms in the world
and then there's Born's Tech
which is a fucking
massive global weapons
manufacturer.
Then there's us.
which is not so great.
So there's windmills.
and there's windmills.
So. what? You wanna give up?
Yeah. they're a big deal.
So what?
Look. part of being a lawyer
is knowing when you're on
to something.
And we're on to something.
All right?
Oh. God.
please don't fuck this up.
This is not me going behind
Donald Cooperman's back.
I wanna be clear about that.
Well. I'm pleased
to hear that. Leonard.
Because it sounded
like you were.
I'm just saying
the case should have settled.
but Cooperman won't do it.
Wait a minute. I'm confused.
I thought it was dismissed.
It was dismissed in state court
when Billy McBride
failed to show.
Then he filed in federal court
where Donald. to his credit.
got it squashed.
even without a hearing.
But then the case resurfaced
in state court.
You must have had a friend
in the clerk's office.
This McBride is desperate.
which to me makes him dangerous.
We should throw some money
at him and make this go away.
But Cooperman is too blinded
by his anger to see that logic
You know what I think?
I think it's a small price
to pay
to make Donald happy.
Cooperman works for us.
He acts like it's
the other way around.
Maybe it is.
Look. do you know what
that guy Larson did here?
What are you talking about?
He worked on the Falcon class
line of fuel systems for the
Navy.
That's not what he did. Leonard.
What do you mean?
Do you actually want
to know what he worked on?
Yes.
No. you don't.
If Donald Cooperman wants
to carry water on this
or anything else.
you know what you job is?
It's to say yes. sir.
Thank you. sir.
Will that be all. sir?
- You wanted to see me?
- I did.
- You wrote a nice brief. Lucy.
- Thank you.
Judge Rosten Keller is sitting.
You've heard of him?
- The Gnome?
- He's a very active gnome.
He asks a lot of questions.
I'm gonna need you there.
should he want specifics
on any of these cases
you've cited.
- Great.
- He's also known
to question second
and third chairs.
He considers any attorney
of record to be fair game.
I'm sure you can guess
my concern.
Well. I've upped my dosage
of Alprazolam.
Come.
Come in.
Smile.
I'm sorry?
I asked you to smile.
Okay. please show me
you can do better than that.
There you go.
I want you to feel that smile
between now and tomorrow.
in the hopes that it might
beget self-confidence.
Judge Keller preys on the weak.
I don't want him looking
at you and smelling blood.
I expect poise and strength.
I won't let you down.
And should Judge Keller
call on you to speak.
I expect you not to stutter.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah. What's up?
Uh. I was just wondering.
would you wanna go grab coffee
with me sometime?
Oh. sweetie.
McBride:
This smells like shit. dude!
I saw your fucking
mouth breather.
You could be a...
McBride: Fucker!
Oh. my God.
Wendell Corey's on line one.
- Wendell.
- Donald. I've been thinking.
This case needs to go away.
- It shall.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
- No later.
Our general counsel.
Leonard Letts?
He's getting nervous.
And he's getting nosey.
Are we done?
You know. I've Ben thinking.
You should come in for a visit.
see what we've got going on.
I'll set it up for
sometime next week.
Sounds good.
Donald?
It needs to go away tomorrow.
Callie Senate is here.
Moo.
Are we ready?
We are ready.
The dog has to stay down.
Callie.
Of all your lieutenants.
why me on this case?
You have talent.
That's it?
Isn't that enough?
There's nothing else in play?
What else can be in play?
Make sure the dog
stays down. Callie.
He's rabid.
Hey.
Handsome. wow.
Just go in there. relax.
Be you.
If he doesn't show up.
can you argue this?
He'll be here.
The hooker just texted me.
so we're fine.
Oh. shit. it's them.
They got that cold "who gives
a fuck about humanity" look.
Walking in a "V" like geese.
Right?
Okay. confidence is key.
You with me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay?
'Cause if you look like
a winner.
then they're gonna think...
No.
All rise.
The Honorable Rosten Keller
presiding.
Oh. my fucking God.
Good morning. Counsel.
Please.
This case seems to be hanging
around like a bad smell.
thanks to my clerk.
Now then.
but I understand there continue
to be problems with the
plaintiff's original filing.
Yes. Your Honor.
The first issue
would be standing.
Your Honor.
before we get to standing...
Hi. I'm Patty Solis-Papagian
for the plaintiff.
We're awaiting the arrival of
lead counsel William McBride.
Judge:
And where is Mr. McBride?
I'm sorry. Your Honor.
The traffic was a mess.
I think the President's
in town or something.
Miss Senate. Miss Kittridge.
and Mr. Letts were all here
on time.
The litigant bringing
the case can't be bothered.
Well. if protocol seems
to count...
- Judge: It does!
- ...I'm seven days early.
Because. you know. the
defendant's required
to provide notice
before scheduling
any motion to dismiss.
Judge: Yes! Well.
we're all here now. so.
Have a seat.
Let's proceed.
The issue concerns standing.
Miss Senate. I'll hear from you.
Thank you. Your Honor.
Rachel Kennedy is neither spouse
nor surviving child
of the deceased.
Wrongful death can be asserted
by anyone financially
or emotionally dependent
on the decedent.
No California court has ever
conferred standing...
My client's brother blew up
on the defendant's boat.
First of all.
Mr. Larson took his own life.
The OSHA report makes
that clear.
And OSHA depended on an
investigation by the defendant.
The issue is standing. counsel.
You're straying off point.
No. actually I'm not.
The point of this lawsuit
is to find out how Ryan Larson
was killed.
I'm granting defendant's motion.
This case is dismissed.
Hang on a second. What?
Your complaint is defective
on standing.
Therefore.
the case is dismissed.
- Thank you.
- Are you kidding?
Do I look like a kidder. sir?
No. but you sound bought.
I hope they paid you well.
Oh. Jesus.
What did you say to me?
I said you sound bought.
I meant you're acting like
a guy who's been bribed
or otherwise in the bag
for the other side.
The case is dismissed.
I'm also fining
Mr. McBride $5.000
for direct contempt of court.
- Excuse me?
- I do not excuse you.
Suggesting
that I've been bought...
that’s contempt.
I'm ordering the plaintiff
to pay full defense costs
for both this proceeding
and the preparation time
connected thereto.
Call my next case.
What the fuck is this?
That vulgarity will cost you
another $5.000.
I don't give a shit.
Make it ten or fifteen.
you douchebag.
Judge: Counsel.
you are dangerously close
to having your ticket punched.
Do you care if you ever
practice law again?
That's a fair question.
And you know what. Your Honor?
We can take that up
at my hearing.
Judge: Where are you going!
McBride: I'm just approaching...
Don't you dare approach
my bench without asking!
Back to your seat. sir.
Alrighty.
Well. like I was saying.
we'll take that up
at my hearing.
because I'm sure
Your Honor knows.
as any good judge would.
even the corrupt kind.
that by holding me in contempt.
you entitle me to a hearing.
a hearing at which I'm allowed
to introduce evidence
including but not limited to
misdeeds by defense counsel.
and here's the good one...
Judicial bias.
That's right. Your Honor.
I said judicial bias.
Just put it on my fuckin' tab.
Judge. schedule my hearing.
What's good for you?
My clerk will propose
a few dates...
No!
...and notify the parties.
I don't understand
what just happened.
Did we just win. or did we lose?
Both. kind of.
Case got kicked.
but we're still open.
That doesn't make any sense.
No. it's the law.
It's not supposed to.
Bottom line is.
is we're still in the game.
That's the good news.
Get back!
Clear back! Come on!
Woman: Somebody call 911!
Man: I will!
Rachel?
Rachel.
You stinker!
Resynced and corrections
by Dan4Jem. XII.MMXVI